《边桥谜案》前情提要
Previously on The Bridge..
我家人在哪
Where is my family?
格斯  你认识一个叫肯尼斯・黑斯廷的人吗
Gus, do you know a person named Kenneth Hasting?
黑斯廷先生
Mr. Hasting?
你是说阿尔玛的同事
The guy who works with Alma?
你有一个美满的家庭  马可
You have a beautiful family, Marco.
-她们在哪  -跟我在一起
- Where are they? - With me.
现在用力握住这个
Now hold on to this very tight.
现在要小心了
Now, careful.
如果你的手离开那个手柄
Take your hand off that lever,
你就只剩五秒钟和你的女儿们说再见了
you only have five seconds to say good-bye to your daughters.
我数三个数
你把它给我
我扔的时候  你就赶快蹲下
三
我是小桑迪
我知道
你认识我爸爸
是啊
你也很出名
我们是怎么认识的
我们有个共同的朋友
谁
丹尼尔・弗莱
Daniel Frye.
为什么黑斯廷要这么做
Why would Mr. Hasting do this?
-没道理啊  -怎么了
- It doesn't make sense. - What?
我们去哪
Where are we going?
你为什么要这样做
Why are you doing this?
你多大了
How old are you?
十九岁
Nineteen.
迦勒也有十七岁了
Caleb would have been 17.
你俩本可能成为朋友
You could have been friends.
迦勒和格斯
Caleb and Gus.
一切都可能
Everything could have been...
大不相同
different.
你打算做什么
What are you going to do?
对你做什么吗
To you?
是的
Yes.
对迦勒而言  那是他母亲的罪孽
For Caleb, it wa the sins of the mother.
对你而言  是你父亲
For you, the father.
他是个好人
He's a good person.
他是个好爸爸吗
Is he a good dad?
他很努力
He wants to be.
努力过就够了  对吧
And it's the thought that counts, right?
仅供学习 禁止用于任何商业盈利行为
更多影视更新
请登陆www.YYeTs.com
翻译
冰蓝
圈圈
屯栗子
爱卿遛小鸟
翻译
胖兔纯
蓬蓬裙
No.Zero
foolyangyang
校对
面条打包子
wdjmhs
时间轴
萌
imok
chance-coco
后期  吉吉
总监  wdjmhs
边桥谜案
第一季   第十集
等等
Hang on a second.
马可  他抓走了格斯  灰色的轿车
Marco. He took Gus. Gray sedan.
2EO  2EO
2-E-O. 2-E-O.
-2EO  -放松点
- 2-E-O. - Take it easy.
我会陪着她
I'll stay with her.
我们在调查他可能把你儿子带去哪里
We're working on where he could've taken your son.
这是怎么回事
How did this happen?
我不知道
I don't know!
我们会找到他的
We're gonna find him.
走吧
Come on.
丹尼尔
Daniel.
开不了车了吧
So much for the wagon, huh?
那是
It's, uh..
"安慰受折磨的人  折磨安逸的人"
"Comfort the afflicted and afflict the comfortable.
你不能就这样溜了
You can't just go AWOL.
-你听说过吗  -听说过
- You ever heard of it? - I've heard it.
好记者
A good journalist..
安慰受折磨的人  折磨安逸的人
comforts the afflicted and afflicts the comfortable.
法利・彼得・德昂[美国幽默作家  新闻工作者]
Finley Peter Dunne.
这话出自他口  我在二十岁时
He said that. I wrote this when I was...
-写下了这段话  -那就成为好记者
- 20. - So be a good journalist;
别喝了  你之前就戒得挺好
quit this shit. You were doing well.
你知道我车里怎么会被人装炸弹吗
You know why I ended up in my car with that bomb?
不知道
No.
我是杀害戴维・泰特妻儿的帮凶
I helped kill David Tate's wife and kid.
解释一下
Explain.
六年前
Six years ago...
我
and I was, uh...
我跟小桑迪・索尔一起鬼混
I was hanging out with Santi Sol Jr.
我们可卡因不够了
And we needed more coke,
他就过边桥去取
so he went back across the bridge to get some.
他撞到了那个女人的车
He clipped that woman's car.
却连车都没停
He just kept going.
是他撞了人  不是你
He did, not you.
正要说到我变成人渣的部分
Yeah, but this-this is the part where I become a shitty human being.
我没有去作证
See, instead of, say, I don't know, testifying,
没有抚平伤痛
instead of comforting the afflicted,
我接受了小桑迪他爸的收买
I just let Santi Jr.'s dad buy me off.
他某天来找我
He just came to me one day
说  "丹尼尔  我吊得很
and he said, "Daniel, I have a big cock,
我在休斯顿有间报馆  你来为我工作吧"
I have a newspaper in Houston. I want you to work for me."
你答应了
And you said yes.
我答应了
I said yes.
我想都没想就答应了
I said yes so fa... I didn't even hesitate.
丝毫没有迟疑
I said yes in two seconds flat.
-所以桑迪才装作不认识你  -是吗
- That's why Santi pretended he didn't know you. - Oh, yeah?
他跟我撇清关系
He big-timed me?
-逼养的  -真讨厌跟醉酒的你说话
- Cooze. - I hate talking to you when you're drunk.
随便啦
Oh, well.
你可以做出改变
You can change.
我试过了  显然我做不到
I tried... but obviously, I can't.
明早七点有个戒酒会  就在这条街
There's a meeting tomorrow, 7:00 a.m down the street.
滚他娘的十二步戒酒法
12 Steps can suck my dick.
让别人帮你吧
Let people help you.
我陪你一起去
Meet me. I'll go with you.
也许我就你一个真心朋友
You might be my only real friend.
太可悲了
That's pathetic.
七点见
7:00 a.m.
-你假装是洁娜给我发短信  -没错
- You texted me saying you were Zina. - Right.
你让我再给他一次机会
And you told me to give him another chance.
是的
I did.
我真的不懂
So I do not understand.
迦勒也是
Neither did Caleb.
-阿尔玛  -马可
- Alma. - Marco.
格斯呢
还是不知下落
快收拾一下你和孩子们的行李
我要带你们去埃尔帕索
我爸和兄弟们要来接我们
跟他们待在一起很安全
他们不会想见到你的
阿尔玛
Alma.
拜托
他差点就杀了你两个女儿  马可
但我阻止了他  她们也都好好的
我们没事是因为他不想杀我们
现在没时间说这个
不能再浪费时间了  我们随后再聊
我不懂
为什么是我们
你们不是朋友吗
因为我把他老婆睡了
行了吧
但那时我还没跟你在一起
那时我还不认识你
但你们是朋友啊
但他们当时吵架了  他们发生了争执
然后她就发生了意外
在她来找我的路上
我对发生在你身上的事非常抱歉
找到格斯
阿尔玛
Alma..
你还想让我说什么  马可
你能活下来很幸运
You're lucky to b alive.
撕裂的伤口很长  但是没伤到器官
That laceration is long, but it didn't damage any of the organs.
那我的胳膊呢
And my arm?
桡骨骨折了  很严重
You fractured the radius badly.
-我胳膊动不了了  -能感觉到吗
- I can't move it. - Can you feel it?
只是因为肿胀而已  还疼吗
That's just the swelling. How's the pain?
还疼
It's there.
我们给你带了点东西来
We brought you some things.
预后是什么
What's the prognosis?
她胳膊需要动手术
Well, she's gonna need surgery on the arm.
近期是不行了
That's not possible anytime soon.
你不能走  桑娅  你差点就送了命
You can't leave, Sonya-- you nearly died.
你不是说我很幸运吗
I thought you said I was lucky.
我说你能活下来很幸运
I said lucky to b alive.
你流了很多血...
You've had a lot of blood loss...
医生  我们能单独待一会儿吗
Doc, could we have a minute, please.
-好  -谢谢
- Sure. - All right.
你应该听从她的建议的
You know, maybe yo ought to listen to her.
格斯有消息了吗
Anything on Gus?
没有  马可正在把阿尔玛转移到安全的地方
Nope. Marco's getting Alma somewhere safe.
能帮我一下吗
Can you help me with these?
当然了  你坐下
Sure, babe. Sit yourself down.
你该留下住院的
You should stay here.
我不能留下  格斯还活着
You know I can't do that. Gus is alive.
何以见得
Why do you say that?
他想让马可痛苦
He wants Marco to suffer.
他想让他也经历一下
He wants to draw it out.
维柯丁[止痛药]  很有效
Vicodin. It-it's good.
好  谢谢你向我们吐露心声  肖恩
Okay. Okay, thanks, Shaun, for trusting us with that.
今天我们这里来了新人
We have a new face with us this morning.
你想让我  也来一遍吗
You want me to do... do the whole thing?
-对  -天哪
- Yeah, yeah. -My God.
好吧  我叫丹尼尔
Um... okay. My name is Daniel.
如果你们叫我丹的话  我会杀了你们的
If you almost call me Dan, the I'll kill you.
太棒了  谢谢你讲了
Stripes. Um, thank you for telling me
一个非常让人郁闷的故事  肖恩
that deeply depressing story, Shaun.
说实话你让我自我感觉很良好
You actually make me feel really good about myself,
这点很棒
so that was awesome.
我大约90分钟前刚喝了最后一杯酒
Um, I had my last drink about 90 minutes ago
味道很不错
and it was delicious.
好吧
Okay.
我不知道你们都是怎么做到的
I don't know how you guys do what you do.
对我来说几乎是不可能的事
It just seems kind of impossible to me.
我尝试了
I tried.
我努力了  但我把自己逼得太紧
I try so hard, and then just, I get so far
结果又搞砸了  当新的问题出现时
and then shit the bed and something happens,
我只好选择灌醉自己
and I just get hammered,
那样日子就过得容易多了
and life is so much better when you're hammered.
但在我生命中
But I have...
仍然有一位好友觉得我可以改过自新
I have cool people in my life who think I can change.
我见到了许多出色的人
I see a lot of cool people,
谢谢你
thank you,
你们让我再一次相信自己
who let me believe in myself.
所以  谢谢你们
So, thanks for that.
天哪
Oh, God.
不管了
So, whatever.
我没带表  但是
I don't have a watch or anything, but, uh, look.
现在是8点22分
It is 8:22...
从现在起我会再试一次
and, uh, from this point on I'm gonna give it a shot.
我不知道能坚持多久
I don't know how it's gonna go but...
但我会努力尝试
Shit, I'll give it a shot.
就这样
Okay.
刚才说的真感人啊
How touching that all was.
大家注意  这些是从戴维・泰特公寓
All right, gang. This is the haul from
搜出来的材料  每个受害者一堆
David Tate's apartment. One pile per victim.
抓紧时间  但一定要仔细
Be quick, but be diligent.
这些东西对我儿子有什么帮助
How does that help my son?
他作案很有计划
We know he's methodical.
如果抓走你儿子是其中一环
If there's a plan for your boy,
这里面一定有些蛛丝马迹
it's in here somewhere.
你也没法确定
You don't know that.
但几率最大
I know it's our best bet.
车牌调查得怎么样了
Anything on the license plate?
还没消息
No, ma'am, not yet.
-你还好吧  -没事
- You okay? - Yeah.
好吧  这有丹尼尔・弗莱的汽车爆炸案
All right. Got Daniel Frye's car bomb here.
盖德曼谋杀案  梅多斯医生谋杀案
Gedman's murder. Dr. Meadow's murder.
你在流血
You're bleeding.
是的
Yes.
一切都弄砸了
Everything is coming apart.
格斯的事我很抱歉
I'm sorry about Gus.
抱歉我没能保护好他
I'm sorry I couldn't protect him.
你已经尽力了
There was nothing you could do.
但这是我的职责  你叫我保护好他的
But it was... it was my job, and you asked me to keep him safe,
但我没能做到  对不起  我尽力了
and I, and I didn't. I'm sorry. I tried.
过来一下
Come here.
-这些是什么  -我们没弄明白的文件
- What are these? - These are documents we can't connect...
-你上一次睡觉是什么时候  -谁知道
- When did you last sleep?  - Uh, who knows?
-你状态很不好  -我没事
- You're not yourself. - I'm fine.
我必须得问你
I'm required to ask.
你确定不需要休息一下
Are you sure you don't need to step away?
这混蛋抓了我儿子  汉克
如果有人抓了你儿子你会怎样
What would you do if someone had your son?
巡警发现了那辆车
Uniforms found the car.
快去
Go. Go, go, go, go.
不  不  不
No, no, no, no, no.
一小时前掘墓人发现它停在这里
Gravedigger found it out here an hour ago.
-里面没东西吗  -操作手册  收据
- Nothing inside? - Manual, receipts,
杂物箱里还有些别的东西
a few things in the glove box.
马可
Marco!
马可  这不是他
Marco. It's not him.
这不是格斯  只是个坟墓
It's not Gus. It's just a grave!
他在耍你
He's playing with you.
我是个男人  是个父亲
I am a man. A father.
这不是儿戏
This is not a game.
我明白  好了  快起来
I know.Come on, get up.
我们不会放弃的  好吗  走吧
We won't stop, okay? Let's go.
埃尔帕索  州法院
好了  是有点麻烦
Okay. Kind of a curveball.
麻烦大了去了
A curve-up-my-ass ball.
我觉得也没那么严重
More like a slider then, I guess.
他什么都没留给我
He left me nothing.
他把房子和土地留给你了
He left you the house and land.
钱  车  艺术品  家具全归凯特了
Kate got the money, the cars, the art, the furniture.
我都说了  你得到了土地和隧道
I repeat, you got the land and the tunnel.
庭审真是很顺利啊
That went super well, I thought.
你还真是善于离间我和你爸啊  凯特
You did a really good job of turning him against me, Kate.
其实有一天
So... this one time,
我爸半夜给我打电话
my dad calls me up in the middle of the night.
我问他出什么事了
And I-I ask him what's up, you know?
他说  不过是又和那个蠢女人过了一天罢了
He says, "Oh... it's jus another day married to an idiot."
那是八年前的事了
That was eight years ago.
所以让他疏远你的人  是你自己
Pretty sure you turned him against you.
-别了  贱人  -再见  凯特
- Bye, whore. - Adios, Kate
别理她
Forget her
看着我  别理她  隧道是我们的
Look at me, forget her We've got the tunnel
不是吗  今天下午我们去把蒂姆的事解决了
Okay? We solve the Tim problem this afternoon,
好好吓唬一下他  然后就没事了
we put the fear of God in him,  and then we'll be fine.
韦德副队长
Lieutenant Wade?
在  但我们现在有点忙
Yeah, we're kind of busy right now.
丹尼尔・弗莱失踪了
Daniel Frye is missing.
-他不是个酒鬼吗  -不是的
- He's an addict, right? - It's not like that.
我们一起去参加戒酒会  我觉得
We were at an AA meeting, an I don't...
我觉得把车开走的  不是他本人
I don't think it was him that drove his car away.
是吗  那是谁开走的
Yeah? Who was it?
丹尼尔帮忙包庇了那场肇事逃逸
Daniel helped cover up the hit-and-run.
就是戴维・泰特家的那场事故
David Tate's family.
他说正因为这样凶手才一直针对他
He told me that's why he's been target all this time.
该死
Damn.
停车罚单
Parking ticket.
就是尸体被遗弃在桥上的那一天早上
From the morning the bodies were left on the bridge.
那是计划之外的
Not part of the plan.
这上面的地址不是他的公寓  是别的地方
This is not his apartment address. It's something else.
快走  路上再请求支援
Come on. We'll call it in on the way.
有人吗  有人吗
Hello? Hello?
有人吗
Hello?
有没有人啊
Is anybody there?!
"青春永驻"疗养院
1962年  埃尔帕索  德克萨斯州
我认识这个人  他会定期来看一位病人
I'm sure of it. He visits one of our residents.
大概隔几周来一次
I'd say every few weeks.
-哪位病人  -钱伯斯先生
- Which resident? - Mr. Chambers.
他现在应该在会客厅
He's probably in the parlor.
是个大好人  和善  心肠也好
He's a nice man. Warm, kind.
您认识他吗
Do you know who he is?
当然了  他是我父亲
Of course. He's my father.
资料里有沃尔特・钱伯斯的家庭住址
Walter Chambers has home address on file.
戴维提到过他的叔叔患有老年痴呆
David once said his uncle had alzheimer's.
戴维・泰特那天来过这里  快走
David Tate was here that day. Come on.
你在干什么
What are you doing?
如果找不到格斯怎么办
What if we can't find him?
-会找到的  -你怎么能肯定
- We will. - You can't say that.
我们俩曾经很多年没有交流
We... hadn't really talked for years,
突然间  他又回到我身边
and then suddenly he was back in my life.
我们之前还聊了很多
We just talked about..
说起我一直不能多陪陪他
how I wasn't there for him enough.
以及我会如何尽力地
And how I'd try to...
弥补这一切
do better.
泰特也是部分原因
Tate set that up too.
但主要还是我的错  而现在
Still. And now I'm gonna...
我却要再次失去他
and now I'm gonna lose him again.
我不敢说我们一定能找到他
I can't say we'll find him,
但不代表我们不会努力找
but you can't say we won't.
如果他不在里面呢
What if he's not inside.
那就接着找
We'll keep looking.
埃尔帕索警察  快开门
El Paso P.D. Open the door!
这就是他存放克里斯蒂娜的腿的地方
That's where he kept Cristina's legs.
格斯
Gus?
-不是  -我的天啊  戴维
- No. - Jesus, David.
格斯长得挺帅的
He's a good-looking kid, Gus.
离他远点  只管冲着我来
Leave him alone. Take it out on me.
我不是正在这么做吗
Well, isn't that what I'm doing?
至少让我跟他说句话
Let me talk to him at least.
这不可能
That's not possible.
-他还活着吗  -暂时活着
- Is he alive? - For now.
我本以为我们会相处得很好
I thought we'd get together.
你为什么要这么做
Why are you doing this?
因为我很生气  想跟你谈谈
Because I'm angry, and I want to talk about it.
好
All right.
没问题  在哪里
Fine. Where?
-你现在在哪  -在你叔叔的家里
- Where are you now? - At your uncle's house.
在听吗
Hello?
我告诉过你的那些事  你竟然还记得
You actually remembered something I told you about myself.
-我们找到那个冰柜了  -我们?
- We found the freezer. - We?
是的  桑娅和我在一起
Yes. Sonya's here with me.
是吗  她怎么样
Really? How is she?
-很憔悴吧  -她很好
- Probably pretty pale. - She's fine.
我本来还想问
I've been meaning to ask her
她对杰克・柴德里斯这种人作何感想
how she enjoy getting to know Jack Childress.
那人对于边境的看法可真是够疯狂的  对吧
That man has some bat shit theories on the border, doesn' he?
戴维  我们到底在哪里碰面
Where are we meeting, David?
先上车  一分钟后打给你
Get in your car. I'll call you in 60 seconds,
再告诉你怎么走
give you directions.
好的
All right.
一个人来  绝对不要带上她
Come alone. Entirely alone, leave her.
我会的
I will.
你不能这样做  完全是顺着他的意
You can't do that. You're doing exactly what he wants.
-把你的枪给我  -不
- Give me your gun. - No.
-求你了  -不  如果你杀了他
- Please. - No. If you kill him, you...
你会坐牢的
you're gonna end up in prison.
桑娅  我需要你的枪  求你了
Sonya, I need your gun. Please.
谢谢  别告诉任何人我去哪了
Thank you. Don't tell anyone where I went.
那我要怎么说
What do I say?
就说  我接到了一个电话  撇下你先走了
Just... that I got a call, and, uh... I left you here.
-我不能对汉克撒谎  -你可以的
- I can't lie to Hank. - Oh, yes, you can.
-不  不行  -很简单
- No, I can't. - It's easy.
就当为了我  好吗
Do it for me. All right?
喂
Hello?
得有人来接我一下
I need a ride.
注意儿童
冰激凌
-小蒂  -雷
- Timbo. - Ray!
-小夏  -我们来这里做什么
- Char. - So what are we doing here?
你这话什么意思
What do you mean by that?
兄弟  这可是鸟不拉屎的地方
Dude, We're on freakin' Mars, right now.
我们觉得这事在荒郊野岭办最合适
We thought a remote area would be best.
好吧
Okay.
迪内罗在哪里
Where's the dinero?
[西班牙发行的一种银币  已退出流通]
你这是发什么疯啊
Look, what-what's going on, crazies?
跪下
Get on your knees.
什么
Wh...?
-我们找到了这个  -这是什么鬼东西
- We found this. - What the heck is it?
是信号发射器  你这个蠢猪
It's a transmitter, dipshit.
在那些枪中找到的
It was in one of those guns.
不  不是的  别误会  没什么大不了
Aw, no, no, no, no, no,no, no, that's-that's nothing.
工厂组装的时候放进去的
They put those things in the at-at the factory.
别再骗我了
Don't even try.
你根本不知道这玩意给我惹了多大麻烦
You have no idea the shit storm you caused me.
怎么了  你跪舔过的女人追着你来了
Okay, what? The lady you muff-dov come-come after you, what?
我不知道你在说什么
I don't even know what that means.
-到底是什么政府部门  -什么
- What part of the government? - Excuse me?
你到底给谁提供信息
For whom are you an informant.
蒂姆  你不说的话
I will get in my truck, Tim,
我就开车从你身上碾过去  我说到做到
and I will run you over. I swear.
好吧  好吧  真的很抱歉
Okay, okay, look Look, I'm sorry, okay?
伙计们  我被抓住了把柄
Guys, I just got caught up in something.
你现在带着窃听器吗
Are you wire right now?
绝对没有  你看
No. No, no, no, no. No, see?
他们连我在哪都不知道
They-they-they don't even know where I am.
烟酒枪炮及爆裂物管理局  就像一盘散沙
ATF, they're, like, so disorganized,
好像把我忘了似的
it's lik they-they forget about me.
烟酒枪炮及爆裂物管理局
The ATF?
杀了他
Shoot him.
我以为你只是想吓吓他
I thought you said we were gonna scare him.
我改主意了
I changed my mind.
-开枪  -我下不了手
- Do it. - I don't think I can.
我们从小玩到大的
We used to play kickball together.
求求你们了  小夏  求你了  是我呀
Guys, it's... come on, Char, dude, it's me.
我们一起开着露营车去毕业舞会
We-we-we took an RV to our prom together.
他说的对
He has a point.
你穿着蓝缎子礼服  头上戴着一朵白色的花
Blue satin. Big white flower in your hair.
把枪给我
Give it to me.
-小夏  -什么
- Char.. - Wha...?
求你了
Please, please..
不要啊  不要
No, no! No, no, no, no, no.
老天呀  不
No, no, no, no, no, no. Oh, no!
-冷静点  -你叫我怎么冷静
- Calm down. - Calm down?
你杀了蒂姆
You killed Tim.
他是我们的伙伴啊
He was our buddy.
你妻子怎么样
How's your wife?
别提起她
Don't talk about her.
我和她睡过了  你知道吗
I had sex with her. Did you know that?
你在撒谎
You're lying.
我真是被她的饥渴吓到了
What surprised me was the vigor.
我亲了她一下
I mean, after that first kiss,
她就开始热烈地回应我
she really threw herself into it.
我要开到哪去
Where am I driving?
她活下来很正常  并不是她的错
It's okay that she survived I mean, it-it wasn't her fault.
也不是格斯的错
It's not Gus's fault either.
没错  但他是你儿子
No, but he's you son.
就像迦勒是我儿子一样
Like Caleb was mine.
戴维  你到底要我去哪
Where am I going, David?
富兰克林山公园
Franklin Mountain Park.
你们在我家上过床吗
Did you do it at my house?
上过
Yes.
在我床上  和我老婆
In my bed with my wife.
你当时打算怎么做
What was your plan?
我没有计划
I didn't have one.
那你觉得只要我没发现就没事是吗
Did you think it was okay as long as I didn't find out?
不是的
No.
想过要告诉我吗
Did you even think about telling me?
-没有  -没错  你就是随心所欲
- No. - No, you just wanted what you wanted.
才不在乎会伤害到别人
Who cares who it hurts?
我快到公园了
I'm getting to the park.
J号停车场  靠近采石场
Lot J, near the quarry.
马可在哪
Hey, where's Marco?
不知道  他接了个电话就走了
I don't know.He got a call and left.
谁打给他的
Got a call from who?
你脸色不好
You don't look good.
没什么
Oh, it's-it's nothing.
好吧  过来  坐下
Okay, come on. Sit down.
你得吃点东西
You need to eat.
-我不喜欢吃香蕉  -顾不了这么多了
- I don't like bananas. - That doesn't matter.
你现在本来是要手术的
You supposed to be on an operating table right now.
我理解为什么你不想做手术
And I understand why you're not,
但如果你太虚弱  生病了或伤势加重
but you will be of no help to Marco and his boy
那就什么忙也帮不了马可和他儿子
if you faint or get sick or get hurt even worse.
我得继续调查
I need to keep looking.
我知道
I know.
我们肯定漏掉什么了
I know we're missing something.
就在那些文件里  我肯定
It's in those documents. I know it.
明白  先把它喝了
Okay. Just drink that.
再接着调查
And then back at it.
好久不见啊  老朋友
Well, hello there. Old friend.
住手
Stop.
他在哪
Where is he?
作为警察  这种感觉挺特别吧
Strange feeling for a cop, isn't it?
那种无力感
To be powerless?
丹尼尔・弗莱的车
Daniel Frye's?
看来你还真是做警探的料啊
That's some amazing detective work.
你把他也杀了
You kill him, too?
你有想起过我吗
Have you thought about me much?
在我自杀后
Since my suicide?
没有
Not much.
你知道我当时崩溃了吧
You knew I was crumble, right?
就在她死后
After she died.
心理医生让我对药物上瘾
A shrink had me hooked on pills.
调查局把我开除了
The FBI fired me.
我听说了
I heard.
但没给我打过一个电话
But not one phone call.
我们失去联络了
We were out of touch.
再见面的方式很有趣
Funny how that happens.
上车
Get in the car.
是她选择了我  戴维
She chose me, David.
你做这么多就是因为她选的是我
All of this because she chose me?
没错
Yes.
你杀了这么多人就是因为你老婆抛弃了你
You killed all these people because your wife left you?
她是从我身边被夺走的
She was taken from me.
失去一切的又不只有你一个人
You're not the first person to lose everything.
那边这样的事情每天都在发生
Over there it happens every day!
很多人的生活都变得支离破碎
People have their lives ripped away from them.
可他们也没去杀人啊
It doesn't make them killers.
可能我比较特别吧
Maybe I'm special.
你才不特别呢
You... you're not.
把手机扔了
Get rid of you phone.
带枪了吗
You have a gun?
-带了  -很好
- Yes. - Good.
我来开车
I'll drive.